Is it too early to say which one's going to go on board order?
Yeah, we really haven't talked to this guy so much.
That will be part of the design plan.
And we've talked extensively with Tuller and I and with FEMA and with own during the grant process of writing the grant on how we would do this.
Because they are all major egress ingress avenues into our city.
They were approved is because they fled.
Normally they fled first.
So we have discussed on detours.
We have detour routes.
We had to provide that to FEMA.
We also know.
Basically, know that we are not going to make it impossible to get around my Emma.
When they are working on the roads.
That's part of that design plan.
Less.
Two.
We'll be part of that.
Should going out to the council.
This is essentially because we haven't.
We just got to take the work we have.
We have a risk.
We're on a time.
But the question is for.
We lend it our own.
Thank you.
We look forward to it.
Second.
Thank you.
Michael.
James.
Hi.
12.
Other than.
Or any of the residents.
It's pushing this agenda.
13 staff reports.
14.
Trustee.
Community announcements.
15.
This may be.
Continue.
From.
California.